# ROMAN JASIEK





Web Developer with 20 years of experience in Sales, +10 years experience as Wordpress Enthusiast and Writer/Blogger who will soon graduate a 1-year intensive remote training in Full Stack Web Development (MERN Stack).

Seeking a position to apply all my experiences, to challenge myself and deliver solution oriented approaches - always with maximum customer satisfaction in mind and implementing the STAR method.

## **CONTACT**

ADDRESS

9

Schillerstr. 47, 39108 Magdeburg

PHONE

+49 - 172 - 4563446

**EMAIL** 

romanjasiek@me.com

WEBSITE

github.com/romanjasiek

SOCIAL MEDIA

linkedin.com/in/romanjasiek/

#### **EDUCATION**

# Full Stack Web Development (MERN Stack)

Digital Career Institute gGmbH | 2021/02 - 2022/01

- Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training including technologies from MERN stack
- Completing a couple of small and one final large practical project to practice programming skills
- Completing several additional courses on platforms like Udemy to learn and practice more

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Team Lead

Amazon Logistik Suelzetal GmbH | 2020

 Workflow controller between different departments in the outbound area of a major logistics center

#### District Manager

Wüstenrot Bausparkasse AG | 2019 - 2020

- Self-employed sales representative according to §84 HGB
- Sale of insurance and financial products

# **Customer Service Representative**

Targobank AG | 2019

 Telephone acquisition of new customers, advising existing customers on topics related to the digital transformation of the bank

#### **Apple Master & Specialist Consultant**

Saturn Electro Handelsges. mbH | 2012 - 2018

- Specialist consultant in the Computer Hardware & Accessories department
- Brand ambassador for Apple Inc.

# ROMAN JASIEK

# WEB DEVELOPER





# **SKILLS**

HTML 5

CSS3 / Sass /SCSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript (ES5/ES6)

MongoDB

**Express** 

React.js

Next.js / Node.js

Git/GitHub

WordPress

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Lightroom

Agile Software Development

German (Mother tongue)

English

#### PORTFOLIO

# **Music Evangelists**

Wordpress

musicevangelists.com

#### **React Portfolio**

React, Sass, JS, Bootstrap

romanjasiek.github.io/portfolio

# **Coding Tunes**

React, CSS

romanjasiek.github.io/vaguemusic-player

### **MERN Social Network**

MongoDB, Express, React, Node

github.com/romanjasiek/thesoci

alnetwork-client

github.com/romanjasiek/thesoci

alnetwork-server

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Sales Representative**

GRAVIS Computervertriebsges. mbH | 2011 - 2012

- Sales advisor for Apple hardware and software of all kinds
- Software support and tutoring, minor hardware repairs

#### **Book Seller & IT Support**

Thalia Bücher GmbH | 2007 - 2011

- Sale of books, management of own merchandise groups (purchase, returns, presentation of products)
- Germany-wide assistance with the transition of the stores to an SAP-based ERP system

# Store Manager (Parental leave replacement)

Weltbild Plus Medien Vertriebs GmbH & Co.KG | 2005 - 2006

- Sales operations
- Personnel planning, applicant selection, and conducting recruitment interviews
- Planning and realization of marketing activities

### Sales Representative

PowerBeam! e.K. | 2005 - 2005

# **Production Helper**

ZAG Zeitarbeits-Gesellschaft GmbH | 2004 - 2004

#### **Book Seller**

Thalia Bücher GmbH | 2002 - 2002

# **Bookseller Apprenticeship**

Thalia Bücher GmbH | 1999 - 2002